Guide to the Occupy Stanford Collection
Stanford University. Libraries.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Occupy Stanford collection
2011
SC1076
Occupy Stanford.
1832.96 megabyte(s) and 3.25 linear feet
Websites, fliers, meeting minutes, and posters documenting the Occupy Stanford movement.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives Green Library 557 Escondido Mall Stanford, CA 94305-6064 Email: specialcollections@stanford.edu Phone: (650) 725-1022 URL: http://library.stanford.edu/spc
Administrative Information
Information about Access
The materials are open for research use. Audio-visual materials are not available in original format, and must be reformatted to a digital use copy.
Scope and Contents
The materials consist of websites, fliers, meeting minutes, and posters documenting the Occupy Stanford movement.
Access Terms
College students--Political activity--California.; Student demonstrations.; Student movements--California--Stanford.
Collection Contents
- Computer files
  - Google Groups website
    https://sites.google.com/site/occupystanford/home Captured 2011 Dec 2
    - 2011 Dec 15
    - 2011 Dec 2, 3.43 megabyte(s)
  - Facebook page, 2011 Dec 15
    http://www.facebook.com/OccupyStanford Stated Mission: "Our goal is to spark discussion on campus and throughout the country about wealth inequality and corruption in the banking sector, corporate America, and in politics. Ultimately, we hope to reform the country so that it more accurately reflects the will of the people. As Stanford students, our mission is to change Stanford's policies so that it acts more responsibly and in the interests of everyone."
  - Fliers, 2011; 6 computer file(s) (PDF)
  - Graphics, 2011
  - Meeting Notes, 2011 Oct 14-31; 5 computer file(s) (DOC)
- Print material
  - Fliers (Box 1)
  - Meeting Notes, 2011 Oct 14-31 (Box 1)
  - Posters, 4 item(s) (Box Sd12)